lockerpulse.com 2014-05-18

# Privacy Policy - LockerPulse

## Statement from Our Team

As avid users of technology and the web, we understand your desire to have your privacy respected. With LockerPulse we've created a service that we ourselves want to use, and that includes managing your private information in the same manner that we want other companies to manage ours. On this page we've done our best to explain in plain English exactly how LockerPulse collects, stores and uses your information. If you have any questions please don't hesitate to email us at .

## Information Collection and Use

### Non Personally Identifiable Information

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This information includes but is not limited to: internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We currently use Google Analytics for this functionality. You can read their privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### Registration

We collect minimal personally identifiable information when you register for an account. We will never share your personally identifiable information with third parties unless we give you prior notice and you make the choice to do so.

The information that we collect includes an email address, username, and password. It is your responsibility to provide an accurate email address and a secure password. Usernames are collected for the sole purpose of creating a friendly user experience (i.e. personalized pages and emails) and as a unique user Log In. Email addresses are collected for the purpose of emailing notifications to users. To gather information about site usage, we track track the frequency of your log-ins to the site. For your security we encrypt your passwords in our database so that even we are unable to view them.

During sign up, you have the option to opt-in to a daily email newsletter. You can change this preference at any time in the Settings section of your account. From time to time we may also send out emails related to your subscription status, the status of the website, or other business announcements. You can opt out of these emails by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email. 

### Account Security

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and of your account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You may not disclose, share, or distribute your password to any third party. If you feel your password has been jeopardized, you may change your password at any time, and as frequently as you wish by accessing the Settings page after you've logged in. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. LockerPulse can not and will not be liable for any loss or damage from your failure to comply with these security obligations.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We link the information we store in cookies to provide you with a personalized experience. We also use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. Your web browser allows you to turn cookies off. This will, however, have a negative impact on the usability of the website. 

### Advertisements

We may use some of your personally identifiable information, such as your favorite sports teams or your general geographic location as determined from your IP address, to present you with targeted advertising. We may also show you ads from third party networks. Currently this is limited to Google AdSense and Google Affiliate Network. You can find their privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### Right to Access, Modify, and Delete Your Personal Information

You have the right to access, modify, and request the deletion of any personal information collected or processed by LockerPulse. You may modify your information by using the Settings page in your account. You may also modify your data or request that your data be deleted by sending an email to 

## Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

## Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information or demographic information. We use this information to monitor site traffic, notify contest winners, as well as to personalize the site. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

## Business Transitions

In the event that LockerPulse or Pure Adapt, Inc goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and notice on our web site of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our blog, and/or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

## Contact Us

Questions about the Privacy Policy can be emailed to
